[tropical music]
[热带音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[creaking]
[吱吱作响]
[romantic music]
[浪漫音乐]
Aah, I'm floating on air.
啊啊，我飘在空中了。
A balloon ride,
a candlelight dinner,
乘坐气球，
烛光晚餐，
and our wedding song is playing!
我们的婚礼歌曲正在播放！
This date is perfect.
这次约会很完美。
No, you're perfect, Karen.
不，你很完美，凯伦。
You're the best computer wife
a copepod could ever have!
你是最好的电脑老婆
桡足类动物可能有！
Bon bon?
邦邦？
Oh, I shouldn't.
哦，我不应该。
Indulge yourself, my darling.
放纵一下自己吧，亲爱的。
Thank you, Plankton!
谢谢你，浮游生物！
This is truly
a date to remember.
这确实是
一个值得记住的日期。
Well, my love, you haven't
seen anything yet!
好吧，我的爱人，你还没有
还没有看到什么！
For you, my love.
为了你，我的爱人。
Ohh, Ray Ray!
噢，雷雷！
[sniffing]
[嗅嗅]
Aah...
啊……
That's right, baby.
没错，宝贝。
Ray Ray is at your service.
雷雷竭诚为您服务。
Ray Ray, you've got my
cooling fans running on high.
雷雷，你有我的
冷却风扇高速运转。
Ha, ha. Get over here
and give me some sugar!
哈，哈。到这里来
并给我一些糖！
[kissing sounds]
[接吻声]
Huh?
啊？
♪ Do do do do do ♪
♪ 做做做做做 ♪
[yawns]
[哈欠]
What a long day.
多么漫长的一天啊。
♪ ♪
♪♪
[kissing sounds]
[接吻声]
[angelic singing]
[天使般的歌声]
Uh... eh... ehh!
呃……呃……呃！
Ahhh!
I can't take it!
啊啊！
我受不了！
What is it, Plankton?
这是什么，浮游生物？
Hold that thought, baby.
保持这个想法，宝贝。
I uh...
I forgot something down here.
我呃...
我把东西忘在这里了。
I'll be right back!
我马上回来！
Can't believe this is really happening.
不敢相信这真的发生了。
Oh!
哦！
The Krabby Patty secret formula
is finally mine!
蟹黄饼的秘密配方
终于是我的了！
Huh?
啊？
Eh...
呃……
Ehh!
呃！
Hm, eh, ah, eh, eh!
嗯嗯嗯嗯！
Is this some kind
of horrible nightmare?
这是某种吗
可怕的噩梦？
What?
什么？
A projector?
投影仪？
You tricked me
with a simulation?
你欺骗了我
通过模拟？
It was a test, Plankton!
这是一次考验，浮游生物！
And you failed!
而你失败了！
You fail every time when it
comes to our romance.
每次你都会失败
来到我们的浪漫。
Right, so I goof up one time
and now I'm the bad guy?
是的，所以我搞砸了一次
现在我是坏人了？
One time?
Failed one time?
一度？
失败一次次？
How about 4,700,000 and...
4,700,000 怎么样？
[glitching]
Error, er-er-error.
[故障]
错误，呃呃错误。
But baby cakes,
但婴儿蛋糕，
I left to go get the
Krabby Patty secret formula.
我离开去拿
蟹黄派秘方。
For me...
And you...
对我来说...
而你...
You know... for us!
你知道...为了我们！
Ehhh?
呃？
Listen, Sheldon.
听着，谢尔顿。
You need to show me
an interruption-free
你需要告诉我
无中断的
romantic date night because
until that happens
浪漫的约会之夜，因为
直到那件事发生
no one is leaving
the Chum Bucket.
没有人离开
密友桶。
[alarm sounds]
[警报声]
Aah!
啊啊！
[intense music]
[激烈的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Oof!
钱币！
You better not mess
this one up, Ray Ray.
你最好别乱来
这个，雷雷。
Ah!
啊!
♪ Da da da da doo doo ♪
♪ 哒哒哒哒嘟嘟 ♪
I think Karen's favorite
"scrap electronics stew"
我觉得凯伦最喜欢
“废旧电子产品炖菜”
ought to do the trick.
应该可以解决问题。
[laughing]
[笑]
Yep.
Huh?
是的。
啊？
I guess it wouldn't hurt
to have just a little peek
我想这不会造成伤害
稍微看一下
at the Krusty Krab.
在蟹堡王。
Hmm.
唔。
♪ Dee dee doo dee ♪
♪ 迪迪迪迪迪 ♪
What a long day.
多么漫长的一天啊。
[yawns]
[哈欠]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[gasps]
[喘气]
It's really out there!
真的就在外面！
And this time
it's not a hologram!
而这一次
这不是全息图！
[scratching and whimpering]
[抓挠和呜咽]
Uh, uh...
呃，呃……
[clearing throat]
Plankton.
[清嗓子]
浮游生物。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Oh, hey, baby!
哦，嘿，宝贝！
Just adding
the finishing touches
只需添加
最后的润色
to tonight's main course!
来今晚的主菜吧！
Aww, you are so sweet!
哇，你真可爱！
I can't wait to try it!
我迫不及待地想尝试一下！
[kissing sounds]
[接吻声]
Whew!
Good one, Plankton.
哇！
好一个，浮游生物。
The formula!
公式！
Now how am I gonna get you?
现在我要怎样才能得到你呢？
[breeze blows]
[微风吹过]
Yes, yes, yes!
是的，是的，是的！
No, no, no!
不，不，不！
Slow it down, you maniac!
慢点，你这个疯子！
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
Who's that?
那是谁？
Krabby Patty!
蟹蟹帕蒂！
Eesh.
It's that numbskull Patrick.
哎呀。
就是那个麻木的帕特里克。
Hey, doofus!
I mean, star friend.
嘿，傻瓜！
我是说，明星朋友。
Krabby Patty.
克拉比·帕蒂。
- Over here.
- Hmm?
- 在这里。
- 唔？
No, over here!
不，在这里！
Come on.
快点。
Yes, that's it.
是的，就是这样。
You've got it.
你已经明白了。
Now who's a good boy?
现在谁是好孩子？
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
Okay, now grab that bottle
by your feet there.
好的，现在拿起那个瓶子
在你的脚那里。
No.
不。
[sighs]
[叹气]
The other drink container
by your feet.
另一个饮料容器
在你的脚下。
- Hmm.
- Pick that one up instead.
- 唔。
- 选择那个。
- Uh?
- By your feet.
- 呃？
- 在你的脚边。
Huh? Uh?
啊？呃？
Now look right!
现在看对了！
Oh, huh!
哦，哈！
You have got to be kidding me.
你一定是在跟我开玩笑吧。
Right, Patrick!
对了，帕特里克！
- Uh?
- Your other right!
- 呃？
- 你的另一项权利！
- Oh!
- Yes!
- 哦！
- 是的！
[laughter]
[笑声]
That's it, huh!
就这样吧，呵呵！
- Ah!
- Good boy.
- 啊！
- 好孩子。
Now bring it over here to me.
Yes, that's it!
现在把它拿过来给我。
是的，就是这样！
Huh?
啊？
Oh, where did he go?!
哦，他去哪儿了？
Excuse me, are you
the window cleaner?
对不起，你是
窗户清洁工？
How in barnacles
did you get in here?
如何在藤壶中
你进来了吗？
- I dunno?
- Well, who cares?
- 我不知道？
- 好吧，谁在乎呢？
Did you bring that bottle
I told you to bring?
你带那个瓶子了吗
我告诉你要带吗？
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Tastes kinda funny, though.
不过味道有点搞笑。
No, I said the other one,
you moron!
不，我说的是另一个，
你这个白痴！
Hey, you guys are doing great!
嘿，你们做得很棒！
Two, three, four.
二、三、四。
A thin piece of glass is all
that stands between me
一块薄玻璃就是全部
挡在我之间的
and what I want most
in the world.
以及我最想要的
在世界上。
Why is life so unfair?
为什么生活如此不公平？
Oh, honey?
哦，亲爱的？
Is dinner almost ready?
I'm famished!
晚饭快准备好了吗？
我饿坏了！
Uh, it's almost finished,
my sweetheart!
呃，快完结了
我的甜心！
What am I gonna do?
我要做什么？
Think, Plankton, think!
想一想，浮游生物，想一想！
Oh?
哦？
Idea!
主意！
That's it!
就是这样！
Karen will never know
the difference!
凯伦永远不会知道
区别！
Now I think I got
what I need right here.
现在我想我得到了
我在这里需要什么。
Patrick, you may
feel a slight tickle.
帕特里克，你可以
感到轻微的痒痒。
Oh, I like tickles.
哦，我喜欢挠痒痒。
[sawing]
[锯切]
Okay, let's get a look at this.
好吧，让我们看看这个。
Ha, ha!
That was intense!
哈，哈！
太激烈了！
Oop!
Almost forgot.
哎呀！
差点忘了。
Ha, ha.
Ow!
哈，哈。
噢！
You're going on a date
with my wife Karen, Ray Ray.
你要去约会
和我的妻子凯伦，雷雷。
Oh, but I sound like Patrick.
哦，但我听起来像帕特里克。
Oh, no.
You keep your mouth shut.
哦，不。
你闭嘴吧。
I will take care of that.
我会处理的。
[high-pitched feedback]
[高音反馈]
[chuckles]
[笑声]
Oh, Karen?
哦，凯伦？
Dinner is served,
my little love nugget!
晚餐已上桌，
我的小爱金块！
Oh, my gosh.
This looks amazing!
哦，天哪。
这看起来棒极了！
I loves my Ray Ray.
我爱我的雷雷。
[growls and giggles]
[咆哮和咯咯笑]
And I love my Karen.
我爱我的凯伦。
Now let's dig in!
现在让我们开始吧！
[giggling]
[咯咯笑]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Krabby Patty secret formula,
here I come!
蟹黄饼秘制配方，
我来了！
Ow!
That's a little rough, Ray Ray.
噢！
这有点粗糙，雷雷。
Ow, Plankton!
What are you doing?
噢，浮游生物！
你在干什么？
Ohh.
Oh, that feels nice.
哦。
哦，那感觉真好。
Ahh, okay. Goodnight.
啊，好吧。晚安。
Whew.
呼。
That was close.
那很接近了。
Yep, we had another
money stacking day.
是的，我们还有另一个
钱堆积日。
Hehehe!
呵呵呵呵！
Didn't we... Huh?
我们不是……嗯？
[gasps]
[喘气]
Me Krabby Patty secret formuler?
我是克拉比帕蒂的秘密配方师吗？
[gasps and screams]
[喘息和尖叫]
It must have fell
out of me boat!
一定是掉下来了
离开我的船！
Ooh, don't you worry, sweetie!
哦，别担心，亲爱的！
Daddy's comin' for ya!
爸爸来找你了！
[tires screeching]
[轮胎的尖叫声]
- Formuler! Formuler!
- Huh?
- 配方师！配方师！
- 啊？
Where are ye, formuler?
配方师，你们在哪里？
Where's me formuler?
我的配方师在哪里？
What have you done
with me secret formuler?
你做了什么
和我一起秘密配方师吗？
Formuler?
Where are ya?
配方师？
你在哪儿？
Formuler?
配方师？
Formuler!
配方师！
Formuler? Formuler?
配方师？配方师？
Formuler!
配方师！
Where are you, formuler?
配方师，你在哪里？
Plankton.
浮游生物。
I know you have me formuler!
So just hand it over!
我知道你有我的配方师！
所以就交出来吧！
Eee...
[blowing]
哎呀……
[吹]
Open up, Plankton!
I know you've got me formuler!
打开吧，浮游生物！
我知道你已经找到了我的配方师！
Huh?
Who could that be?
啊？
那会是谁？
Uh, that banging noise?
呃，那种撞击声？
Haha, that's just the dryer.
哈哈，这就是烘干机。
I thought I'd do the laundry
so you wouldn't have to later.
我想我会洗衣服
这样您就不必稍后再这样做。
Kiss kiss.
亲吻。
Oh, Ray Ray!
That's the most romantic thing
哦，雷雷！
这才是最浪漫的事情
you've ever said!
你曾经说过！
[kissing sounds]
[接吻声]
Hmm.
唔。
The formula is finally mine.
公式终于是我的了。
[chuckling]
[轻笑]
Oh, come on!
哦，来吧！
I know you're in there,
Plankton!
我知道你在里面
浮游生物！
- Wha?
- Eh, eh!
- 世界卫生大会？
- 呃，呃！
Formula.
公式。
Thanks for holding it for me.
谢谢你帮我拿着它。
[both straining]
[双方都紧张]
- Urgh!
- It's mine!
- 呃！
- 这是我的！
Sheldon?
谢尔顿？
Today made up for everything.
今天弥补了一切。
So I wanted to give you
a little something.
所以我想给你
一点东西。
After years of research,
I finally synthesized the data
经过多年的研究，
我终于综合了数据
and came up with the Krabby
Patty secret formula!
并想出了蟹蟹
帕蒂秘方！
[gasps]
[喘气]
A-ha!
啊哈！
Plankton!
浮游生物！
Let go!
松手！
Whatever you say, Krabs!
不管你说什么，蟹蟹！
Doh!
Aah!
哎哟！
啊啊！
Who needs your stupid
hard copy in a bottle, anyway
谁需要你的笨蛋
无论如何，硬拷贝装在瓶子里
when I have a downloadable
version right here?
当我有一个可下载的
版本在这里吗？
[groans]
You jerk!
[呻吟]
你这个混蛋！
[chuckling quietly]
[轻笑]
Now...
现在...
the secret formula is...
秘密公式是...
Is what? Is what?
What is it?
是什么？是什么？
它是什么？
[gasps]
[喘气]
Uuugh!
呃！
Ray Ray!
雷雷！
[chuckles nervously]
[紧张地笑]
Uh, which one of us is Ray Ray?
呃，我们当中哪一个是雷雷？
I am, you doofus!
我就是，你这个笨蛋！
Well...
well, I'm Ray Ray too!
嗯...
好吧，我也是雷雷！
No, I'm Ray Ray!
不，我是雷雷！
I don't care
who is the real one!
我不在乎
谁才是真人啊！
You can both watch
this formula get deleted.
你们都可以观看
该公式被删除。
Eee, Karen!
Darling, sweetie!
呃，凯伦！
亲爱的，亲爱的！
Please, let's talk about this!
拜托，我们来谈谈这个吧！
[hysterical crying]
[歇斯底里的哭泣]
Don't mess with date night, Plankton.
别搞乱约会之夜，浮游生物。
Aaah...
啊啊……
Oh.
Nom, nom.
哦。
名义，名义。
Now this is truly
a wonderful date, Plankton.
现在这确实是
一次美妙的约会，浮游生物。
And thank you for giving me
your undivided attention.
谢谢你给我
你的全神贯注。
I wouldn't miss it
for the world, baby.
我不会错过它
为了世界，宝贝。
- Aah.
- ♪ La da dee la da lee! ♪
- 啊啊。
- ♪ La da dee la da lee！ ♪
♪ ♪
♪♪
Oh, boy.
哦，男孩。